<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><metadata>
<idinfo>
<citation>
<citeinfo>
<title>Forest Service Regional Boundaries (Feature Layer)</title>
<onlink>https://apps.fs.usda.gov/arcx/rest/services/EDW/EDW_RegionBoundaries_01/MapServer/1</onlink>
</citeinfo>
</citation>
<descript>
<abstract>An area encompassing all the National Forest System lands administered by a Region. The area encompasses private lands, other governmental agency lands. All National Forest System lands fall within one and only one Administrative Region Area. Metadata</abstract>
<purpose>An area encompassing all the National Forest System lands administered by a Region. All National Forest System lands fall within one and only one Administrative Region Area.</purpose>
</descript>
<keywords>
<theme>
<themekt>None</themekt>
<themekey>geospatial</themekey>
</theme>
</keywords>
<accconst>None</accconst>
<useconst>The USDA Forest Service makes no warranty, expressed or implied, including the warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose, nor assumes any legal liability or responsibility for the accuracy, reliability, completeness or utility of these geospatial data, or for the improper or incorrect use of these geospatial data. These geospatial data and related maps or graphics are not legal documents and are not intended to be used as such. The data and maps may not be used to determine title, ownership, legal descriptions or boundaries, legal jurisdiction, or restrictions that may be in place on either public or private land. Natural hazards may or may not be depicted on the data and maps, and land users should exercise due caution. The data are dynamic and may change over time. The user is responsible to verify the limitations of the geospatial data and to use the data accordingly.

As a work of the United States Government, these data are within the public domain of the United States. Additionally, The U.S. Forest Service waives copyright and related rights in the work worldwide through the CC0 1.0 Universal Public Domain Dedication (which can be found at https://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/).</useconst>
</idinfo>
<metainfo>
<metd>20181018</metd>
<metc>
<cntinfo>
<!--no contact person or organization name available-->
</cntinfo>
</metc>
<metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
<metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
<mettc>local time</mettc>
</metainfo>
</metadata>
